collegeaffiliates.com 2007-04-27

# College Affiliates .com - Privacy Statement

**College Affiliates**

**Privacy Policy**

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. 

**We recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy** and our policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' needs. 

**What Information Do We Collect?** **  
**Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

**Web Site Use Information**  
Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and web server log files to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. 

**What Are Cookies?**  
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function as effectively when viewed by the users. **A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.**

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**  
Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our clients. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your cookies. 

**IP Addresses**  
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses may be automatically collected by web servers as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.  

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites, which have a link on our Website, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. 

_**Our Commitment To Data Security:**_

Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your Country of residence or citizenship. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**A Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 14) use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians. 

**Policy Modifications  
** We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will post any changes here. 

Thank you for visiting our website.
